bykoket.com 2018-11-28

# KOKET | Privacy Policy

**KOKET Privacy Policy – Last updated May 23, 2018**

KOKET operates [http://www.bykoket.com](http://www.bykoket.com/) and [http://www.lovehappensmag.com](http://www.lovehappensmag.com/). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of these Sites. We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving these Sites. By using these Sites, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

**Summary**

KOKET collects your data strictly to provide you with access to our news, special campaigns and events. We will not share this data with anyone unless you explicitly consent to us doing so. We honor your right to privacy and will comply with your wishes to remove your data from our systems.

This Privacy Policy only covers information collected through these Sites and does not cover any information collected offline by us, including information collected by our 3rd Party Wholesale Retail partners.

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

You deserve to know how we collect and use the data you provide to us, and that’s what we are providing you with this page. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on any Sites belonging to KOKET: [http://www.bykoket.com](http://www.bykoket.com/) and [http://www.lovehappensmag.com](http://www.lovehappensmag.com/). This notice was updated in May 2018 to reflect General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) compliance standards.

**Information Collection and Use**

While using our Sites, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. We use the data you provide to us for the following purposes:

  1. Provide you with access to the content and campaigns we produce.
  2. Analyze profile or behavioral data to help us improve the products we offer to you.

We will store this information to keep you informed about other relevant products that may be useful to you.

We will never use or share the information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.

Some information, such as IP and your email address, may be shared with the following third parties who help us run our website and email programs. They will only use this information to serve our needs and are prohibited from using it in any other instance. They are: Google (ad serving and website tracking), Salesforce (CRM - customer relationship management software), Mailchimp (email marketing platform), Facebook and Instagram (ad serving) and LiveChat (chat and help desk).

**Consequences of Failure to Provide Consent**

Consenting to allow us to process and store your data is optional. However, failure to provide that consent will prevent us from delivering the content, campaigns and other experiences to you as mentioned above.

**The Information We Collect**

Across our web platforms, you will be presented with the opportunity to sign up for newsletters, submit your information to access content such as prices, technical information of our products, and apply for eligibility to certain events and special campaigns.

The type of information collected on those pages generally includes but is not limited to:

  * Email address
  * Name
  * Job title
  * Location
  * Company name
  * VAT/Tax ID
  * Mailing/billing address

Based on the information you provide to us, we may create or append other information to your profile in the interest of better serving you (for example, your interests). As is the case with all data we collect, this will be kept private and for our business purposes only.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Like many sites, KOKET uses "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Sites.

**Your Rights**

At any time, you have the right:

  * to request access to or a copy of any information which we hold about you;
  * to rectification of your information, if you consider that it is inaccurate;
  * to ask us to delete your information, if you consider that we do not have the right to hold it;
  * to withdraw consent to our processing of your information (to the extent such processing is based on previously obtained consent);
  * to ask us to stop or start sending you marketing messages;
  * to restrict processing of your information;
  * to data portability (moving some of your information elsewhere) in certain circumstances;
  * to object to your information being processed in certain circumstances.

Any request for access to or a copy of your information must be in writing and we will endeavour to respond within a reasonable period and in any event within one month in compliance with data protection legislation. We will comply with our legal obligations as regards your rights as a data subject.

**How long will we keep your information?**

We will keep your information for as long as you have your account, or as long as is needed to be able to provide the services to you, or (in the case of any contact you may have with us) for as long as is necessary to provide support-related reporting and trend analysis only.

If reasonably necessary or required to meet legal or regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce our Terms and Conditions, we may also keep hold of some of your information as required, even after you have closed your account, or it is no longer needed to provide the services to you.

Where we are permitted to send you direct marketing communications we may retain your contact information necessary for this purpose, (if you have consented to receiving them) for as long as you do not unsubscribe from receiving the same from us.

**Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us but, remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Passwords**

Your account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. KOKET will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and account information. Remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window to help ensure that others cannot access your personal information.

**Our Commitment to The Security of Your Data**

To prevent unauthorized parties from accessing your data and maintain the accuracy and cleanliness of our own data while ensuring the correct use of it, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Specific Issues for The Disclosure of Personal Data To Third Parties**

KOKET respects that the personal data you have provided us is confidential. With that in mind, we will not disclose your personal data to other third parties without obtaining your permission first.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 23 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

**How to Ask Us to Delete Your Data**

If you would like to unsubscribe from our communications at any time, you may do so in the footer of any of our emails. If you would like us to delete your information entirely, or request the information we store about you, contact Marta Vieira, KOKET´s Digital Marketing Director, at mvieira@bykoket.com. Otherwise, by continuing to interact with our emails and services, you provide us with permission to manage and use your data as described above.

**Contact Us**

Questions about our privacy policy or how we use data? Email Marta Vieira, KOKET’s head of Digital Marketing: [mvieira@bykoket.com](mailto:mvieira@bykoket.com).
